(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-15T23:37:10.800662",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ah, you...
There is no one I adore more.
You...
who must have risked life and limb...
to be here with me...
forevermore.
The last words I wrote before I was cast...
...into this endless abyss...
...by the immortals seeking to protect this world and all of its inhabitants.
Wrapped in darkness...
...alone...
...void of all emotion...
I once more feel a presence signaling my return...
...Love's fervent seal...
...a spark of light in this ocean.
Now, there is but little left for you to do before I am free...
...and we can be together.
And those who trapped me within these pages shall rue locking away this beauty forever.
Only your love can set me free.
Go, recite the verse before you quickly.
Must before me you bend and take a knee.
Love Me, Love Me, Love Me
Once in a far away, far away world
Was a collar that coiled like a snake
"I want someone, please! I need someone, please!"
Oh, I listened close as it howled and it neighed
"Please don't be angry and please don't abandon me!"
"Don't leave me here on my own, okay?"
It wrapped itself tightly, daily and nightly
Only with praise would it loosen its hold!
I placed in the top of my class!
There's no one left for me to surpass!
Don't I look cute in this dress?
I really, really must confess...
It's tightening 'round my neck!
Give me your love, all of your love!
Give me your love, all you can conjure up!
Give me your love, all of your love
Till you go mad with ecstasy!
All of the hurt, all of the ache
Help me escape, take it, oh take it away!
Is there no end to this pain?!
Grow as you may, but the necklace will stay
just as small as the day it was found.
It's suffocating, the endless placating,
no one is, no one is ever enough.
Won't lose to anyone, always rank number one,
aren't I a beautiful child?
Hey! Better than her, I'm better than him,
oh, everyone come round and gawk at perfection!
Meeting you right after school
and finally confessing to you,
ain't it too good to be true?
A girl like me in love with you,
who's miserable, vulgar, and crude?
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love,
you can have everything if I have you.
I can have you,
shoulder my load, now yours to behold,
still not enough, you're not enough,
never enough, still I won't lose in my love!
Truly I'm so sorry!
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love,
all you can conjure up,
give me your love, all of your love,
till you go mad with ecstasy!
I know it hurts, only gets worse,
God, how it hurts, soon you'll be craving more pain!
This is my happiness!
Is this my happiness?
Did you enjoy my lovely song?
I hope you did.
It was for you, after all.
But... why are you not smiling?
Are you not happy to see me?
Well?
Say something.
Answer me!
Who... who are you?
What?
You don't know who I am?
But everyone knows.
You are the one that released me, right?
I'm... I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
For releasing me?
No, no, no! For upsetting you!
If I said something wrong, I apologize!
Apologize?
You, who should be amongst my most dearest and beloved followers,
who has freed me from that prison,
who has shown me your love above all others...
You then act like you don't even know who I am?
Why would you toy with my emotions?
I'm... I'm sorry. I'm not sure what you mean.
You're not sure what I mean?
Are you mocking me now?
If you truly do not know who I am,
then why is it that you set me free?
If not for my love, and if not by your love, then for what?!
Tell me the truth! And the whole truth, now!
No more lies, or there will be consequences!
I-I'm not lying!
I swear to you, I have no idea how I released you!
I just came to the temple to collect rare spices and memories
from the many books stowed away here!
By the gods, that's the whole truth!
Extract... memories... from books?
Are you telling me you're a witch?!
How dare you step foot here?!
Even knowing the long history between demons and witches, you still dare step foot here?!
I know how witches dare to try and bind my kind!
Would you be foolish enough to dare attempt that on me?!
Yes! Okay! Yes, I'm a witch!
But I've never... well... mostly never tried anything like that!
I... I swear!
And this time, I was not led on by my nature at all! No!
This time it was an angel that told me of this place!
An angel came to me in my dreams!
...told me of an enchanted book
with centuries of memories stowed away here.
Can you imagine the knowledge and stories
hidden in centuries of memories?
With a prize like that,
I had to come find the book,
no matter the danger.
Little could I have known the true nature of the book, though.
Enough!
I've heard enough.
I believe you are who you say you are:
a witch.
But I don't fully believe your childish story.
No angel would ever lead a witch to such a dangerous book.
And I can hardly believe it is just the book and not myself you are after.
It— It's true!
An angel came to me in my dreams and told me to come here.
I was drawn to that book,
with all its power and stories.
And well, I guess... you inside it.
The powerful aura it gave off drew me right to it.
How was I to know that the allure was thanks to a demon trapped within its pages?
Oh, I guess...
Though, now that I recount my story, it does seem it really was me who released you.
Speaking of coming and going,
now that you are free, I think it is time I take my leave of this place.
I'm glad I was able to help free you from... from whence you came.
I didn't say you could leave.
You may leave when I say you can leave.
And stop your nervous fidgeting.
I'm no fool.
You think I didn't see you reaching for your book of magic?
You, a witch, should know better than anyone
that no amount of magic is powerful enough to destroy a demon of my power.
However, you can take some small solace
in the fact that if I had wanted you dead, you'd already be so.
The only reason you're still alive is because you helped free me.
Alas...
I cannot allow a witch who so obviously came with the intent to bind me to her will leave here freely.
Your story did little to convince me your aims were otherwise.
So I will give you an ultimatum.
You serve me here in my hollow temple.
Love me, adore me...
...worship me.
Every living day, give me all the love you have...
...or I can take your soul right now.
Your choice.
Kiara!
I need you!
Lost in the rain with no umbrella
Night's now out, your eyes
Can't seem to find your way back home
Come in and be my guest
Such a lovely smile spread across your face
But it's simply forgery
If you need to hide from the world outside
Why not try to be my guest?
Waiting all day long, but your friends don't come
And you're left there all alone
Still, you can jump off from the high rooftop
So come on and be my guest
Watch the cat, the way I step and step and step
Very carefully, my feet go tap and tap and tap
They follow nicely with the snap and snap and snap
So lovely, you'll be mesmerized by me
My institution's peaceful as can be
Despite the way that it seems
Both our quotes and our supports will be concise, clear and clean
Since we're only starting out, there's some improbabilities
But just listen up tonight, you'll have to stay up fully
No, I don't like you when you know it's true
Still, you're at their beck and call
Since you desperately give in easily
Come inside and be my guest
You're the last to choose, but you're left confused
Seems that someone took your share
If you won't accuse 'cause you don't have proof
Take a chance and be my guest
On the way back home, there's a sweet aroma
That tempts you off your path
I can't help but laugh 'cause I know in fact
...bound to be my guest
You!
Demon!
How dare you kill an innocent?!
Excuse me?
I've done no such thing.
Innocent?
I would hardly call a witch who lives for power and binds my kind for her own purposes innocent.
The very idea is laughable.
Leave.
I have no quarrel with you, so go now in peace...
...before I change my mind.
A small token for your past bravery and trials.
How gracious.
Don't think I can't see straight through your ploys, though.
You will not escape justice!
Not this time.
You have brought this fight on yourself for your actions, demon.
You have brought all of this on yourself!
For what?
For killing a mere witch?
She was not just a witch!
She was my friend!
And a kind-hearted person!
And you killed her...
...in cold blood!
Oh...
The legendary Phoenix, the mighty, fiery Kiara...
...friends with a witch?
It's almost funny.
Did you not realize?
It was your witch friend who freed me!
Liar!
She would never do such a ghastly thing!
I trust she would stay away from the dark magics and demonic rituals.
To suggest otherwise is just another one of your dark lies!
She didn't deserve to die.
Poor Phoenix.
Still so trusting of those around you and unable to see through their deceptions.
Your kind spirit constantly deceives you.
That witch was never your friend.
We all know they cannot be trusted.
Even after all these years, you still have not changed.
Still believing in lies and still so easily misled.
Still such a fool.
It is you who is the fool, demon!
Your lust for love and attention continues to lead you down the path of death and destruction.
And you don't even see that you're the one destroying your own happiness.
The gods were right to confine you there.
You, who are still shackled by your lust for love...
...your desire for attention...
...your desire to be worshipped!
I am the Demon of Sound!
How dare you speak to me in such a manner!
It is but right that all should worship me on their knees...
...their love for none but myself!
Leave.
I have heard enough of your falsities.
This is your last warning.
Go now, or you'll be left to rot here forever!
I am not afraid of you, and I will heed no such warning!
Listen, and listen well, demon!
I will not allow you to claim any more victims!
To be banished in the void was not sufficient enough punishment for you.
Mm-mm. No.
Now, I will finish what the gods should have!
Come on and get moving 'cause now I'm on a roll, oh
One chance to choose it, so what, you'll rage or bow above, below
You either win or not, can't ever be a draw
Oh, oh, oh, yeah! Open the curtains up!
Mouths start running, lacking money, smoking with us, sick art, sick art
Acting funny, asking if I'm winning with a...
Make your bets, black or red, chips to spend, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Raise the stakes, play the ace, risk your life on a single gaze
Stay with me, all of it will change your fate!
Now here to play, don't get in my way, I'm tired of talking
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, sit down, sit down
One, two, three, one, two, three
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
I got skills as cold as ice, you gotta throw your hands up if you can't decide, gonna scare you off as I roll the dice, huh?
Business guy, I'll say goodbye, yeah!
Hard enough, you make a bluff, enough, enough, enough, yeah
Need the light 'cause weak in mind, it's up, it's up, it's up
I'm standing round, try to avoid the voices in my head
No stopping now, I just gotta win this game instead
Get out of my way
You bet I'm here to stay, and now it's time to learn your place
Hot streak is running, lucky money, smoking like a cigar, cigar
Acting so funny, answer if I'm quitting, well I'm not
Make your bets, black or red, chips to spend, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Raise the stakes, play that ace, risk your life for a single game
Stay with me, yeah, yeah, yeah
Or I will change your state
Got a game to play, don't get in my way, I'm always counting
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
Sit down, sit down
I'll say goodbye, bye!
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
Sit down, sit down
I'm so sorry.
IRyS... It has been so long.
Nerissa! I'm so, so sorry this happened to you. It was not my intention.
What do you mean? What was not your intention?
This... You being... Then the witch and Kiara, too.
What? Are you saying you sent the phoenix here to slay me?
No, I didn't! Well, yes, but it was not my intention!
IRyS, what are you trying to tell me? That you tried to kill me?
You were supposed to be my friend. We've been friends since the beginning.
Yes, of course!
You sent Kiara to kill me?
No! No!
Then what?
Be clear! Or is this how you greet your beloved friend after so long?
No! I... I would never send someone to kill you.
But, yes, I'm still your loyal friend. I always have been, and always will be!
I... I tried to free you, and I did! I sent the witch, Shiori, here to free you, and she did!
But I didn't know she was friends with Kiara and would summon her here if threatened! I thought she would come alone! This was not supposed to happen! It was not my intention!
You sent... a witch... to free me?
Why would you send one who binds my kind for power?
Of all those in the world, a witch?
Why not send one of my most beloved followers? Only they are said to be able to free me.
Explain yourself! What's going on?
I'm... I'm sorry. I have a lot to explain, but we don't have time now. We need to go, now!
Death is coming for you.
What?
Please, come with me! I know a way in which we can hide from Death! We have to leave now before it's too late!
I'm not going anywhere with you until you explain to me what is going on now!
Why would you send a witch to free me, IRyS?
Really, I had no choice!
You had no choice? You could have sent one of my followers instead!
You don't have any more followers! They're all dead! They all died long ago...
What?
No, th- That can't be... Has it been that long?
It's been over a thousand years since you've been locked away,
and your followers, they're all gone now.
It's been many long years since your name was whispered in these lands.
You mean... they no longer love me?
I'm... I'm sorry. I tried to free you as fast as I could. I really did.
But it took a long time to work out how to free you, and there was so much going on. And the Gods weren't about to look kindly on any trying to undo their work, either. I'm sorry.
I don't have time to explain everything right now.
I understand.
Tell me.
Do you still love me?
What?
Yes, of course!
Then why did you lie to me?
I... I'm not lying, Nerissa!
Enough!
You, of all people,
should understand that a witch wouldn't be able to resist the power in my book
and attempt to bind me!
And you can hardly expect me to believe
that you, one of both planes, didn't know of the witch's connection to such a famed warrior?
This wasn't an attempt to free me.
This... this was an attempt to kill me!
To be free of me, to do what the gods couldn't!
Get back!
Nerissa, that's not true!
You don't understand.
Please give me some time to explain!
But... but not here!
Death is coming for you! We have to go!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
Nerissa!
Surely by now, Kiara's soul has arrived before Death!
And when Death finds out that you were free again...
We don't have much time!
We have to go, now!
Please, Nerissa!
No! I don't believe you!
You've broken my spirit.
To learn that my followers no longer love me was one thing,
but to discover that my closest and most loyal friend
has betrayed me, tried to kill me...
and... no longer loves me, too!
If you no longer wish to give me your love,
then I will take it!
Missing Promise
遠ざかり始めた
Starting to drift further away,
その背中はもう振り返らない
that back will no longer turn around.
長い夜が明けても
Even if the long night dawns,
過ちと罪は今もずっと消えずに
mistakes and sins remain without ever fading.
落ちる夕日
The setting sun,
闇が忍び寄り
darkness creeping closer,
黒く染まっていく呪縛
a curse dyeing everything in black.
想うほどに
The more I think about it,
どうして
why did I...
傷つけ試した
hurt and test you?
何度間違い続けた日々を
Unraveling the days of repeated mistakes,
ほどいて結び直すように
as if to rebind them once more,
迷っても逢いに行くよ
even if I lose my way, I'll go meet you.
悲しい涙は拭って
Wiping away these sorrowful tears,
いつの間にか忘れていた
I had forgotten before I realized it,
その優しい声を探して
searching for that gentle voice.
また手を握り合えたなら
If we could hold hands once again,
君ともう一度約束を
I would make a promise with you one more time.
途切れそうな可能性
So as not to lose sight of
見失わないように追いかけて
a possibility about to snap, I chase after it.
手に入れたものなら
If what I obtained
理想とは違う どこか欠けた愛情
was different from my ideal, a somewhat flawed affection...
怒り 嘆き 歪めたまま ぶつけ合う逆さまの言葉
Anger and grief distorted, hurling inverted words at each other.
想うほどに どうして 許せなかった
The more I cared, why couldn't I forgive?
守りたかった笑顔を
The smile I wanted to protect,
気づけば壊して
I broke before I even realized it.
たとえすれ違い離れていても
Even if we pass each other by and drift apart,
君を信じられたなら
if I could just believe in you,
また逢える日が来たかな
I wonder if the day we meet again would come?
ふたり懐かしい顔で
With familiar faces on both of us,
何気なく過ごしていた
if we were to look back on those days
あの頃を思い返すなら
we spent so casually...
ありのまま通じ合えてた
We understood each other as we were,
まるで運命のように
as if it were fate.
なくしたものがもう
Knowing that what was lost
戻らないこと
will never return,
分かっていても 願いをかけること
even so, I cannot stop
やめられはしない
making a wish.
いつか どれほど大切な人だったのか
Someday, I came to realize how precious you were
胸が苦しい度に 知った
each time my heart ached.
共に過ごした日々を...
The days we spent together...
笑い合いたい日々を
The days when we wanted to laugh together...
何度間違い続けた日々を
The days when we kept repeating mistake after mistake...
ほどいて結び直すように
To untie and re-knot them anew,
迷っても会いに行くよ
Even if I get lost, I'll go to see you.
悲しい涙はぬぐって いつの間にか忘れていった
Wiping away sad tears, before I knew it, I forgot them,
その優しい声を探して
Searching for that gentle voice.
また手を取り合えたなら
If we could hold hands once more,
君ともう一度約束を交わそう
Let us exchange a promise with you once again.
Kiara...
...dead?
Huh, never thought I'd see the day.
But tell me, what laid you low?
I must know. Is there a few that could bring this about?
And even fewer who would give you reason to voyage on through my blackened halls...
...and not return to the world of the living as a hatchling?
Must be urgent, whatever it is.
Forgive me...
...but I felt this was something you needed to hear urgently.
I was slain by one with whom you are quite familiar.
A tyrant of darkness.
One out to bring all the world under her domain...
...to worship her for all eternity.
It can't be.
I'm afraid the Demon of Sound has been freed from the Void again...
...and is in the world once more.
Her long confinement has ended...
...and she is the same as she has ever been.
Quick to anger, blinded by her lust for adoration.
And this time...
...I was the second victim of her lust for love and blood.
You?
Murdered by that love-obsessed demon?
Yes.
And her first victim was a good friend of mine, too.
Forgive me, Lord Death, but...
...this injustice cannot stand!
Unfortunately, her power is already beyond my ability to stop.
Please!
You must do something to stop that demon!
That monster...
...she will surely only take more lives...
...and plunge the world into further chaos!
Come on! Quick!
Ascend to the world of the living with your great scythe in hand...
...and reap the life of the Demon of Sound before she can claim another victim!
Avenge my life, and the life of my friend!
I beg you!
That demon cannot be left to ravage the world once more.
I warned the other gods before, but here we are.
It is time I take this into my own hands...
...and do what I should have done long ago!
Huh. Your demonic side was always to be the death of you, IRyS.
Don't you dare speak her name!
Silence!
Your bloodlust and desire for adoration has clouded your judgment...
...to the point where you can't even tell friend from foe anymore!
You're the one who brought bloody doom upon your own beloved friend...
...and yourself!
Your fear of losing your hold over things brings about the very result you so fear!
How dare you?!
Continue on with your excuses.
Blame who you will for your own wrongdoing if you wish.
In the end...
...you have only yourself to blame for the situation you find yourself in.
A lust for love so strong that those you loved turn away.
A desire for power so overwhelming...
...those you have power over turn on you.
An anger so deep that you destroy all who might have helped save you.
Your fate has been sealed by your own hand.
And now...
...I am now here to deliver it to you.
Why do you get to decide who lives or dies?
You, who sits alone in your own realm...
...empress of all, both life and death at your fingertips?
Could you possibly know
about the desire for the love and adoration of others?
You, who already has everything...
You and all the gods, all full of yourselves
and so ready to look down upon those of us who fight for more.
Mouths full of twisted tongues...
Their hearts rot with jealousy.
They're jealous...
...of me!
Spiteful that I was loved more!
Again, you cannot see past your own desires.
The gods took pity on you and your kind.
When I created you, the first demon,
the gods felt it unjust and dangerous for such a being to exist
for the sole purpose of watching over the surface in my stead...
...to be mindless...
...soulless.
So, they gave the demon a psyche
and plucked it from my deepest and blackest halls,
freeing it to roam amongst the two worlds whenever it pleased.
I warned them that the demonic nature was too strong and dangerous to give such desires,
and far too dangerous for such a being to exist alongside the mortals,
but the others persisted. And now...
...here we are, my unheeded warnings leading us back to where it all started.
You almost plunged the world into chaos due to your unbridled lust for adoration.
Time and time again, you gave in to your nature.
Banishing you to a void was supposed to be a chance for you to reflect on your past,
but it's only proven that you are truly unfit for this world.
アイアイアイヘッチュー　なななななんですの
I-I-I hate you! W-W-W-What is this?
キミがいなけりゃ　アタシはナイナイ
Without you, I'm nothing at all.
アイアイソーデスネ　その通りです
Yes, yes, that's right! Exactly as you say!
喉を過ぎれば　かいのありよう
Once it passes down my throat, it's worth taking.
アイアイアイヘッチュー　なななななんですの
I-I-I hate you! W-W-W-What is this?
キミは軽薄　くたびれだらく
You are shallow, exhausted, and self-indulgent.
アタシ一言じゃいられない
I can't just stay quiet with one word.
それはツネにつねにひしひし
That's always, always hitting me hard.
アナタ WHY WHY DON'T YOU KNOW
You, why, why don't you know?
だってダメダメですの
Because it's totally no-good!
意味があるなら言葉にせずに
If it has meaning, without putting it into words,
タダシイタイドデ示されなきゃ
unless you show it with proper attitude,
すべてが伝わらないままになる TOP SECRET
everything will remain uncommunicated. Top secret!
散落とさないように　騒げ！
So as not to scatter and lose it, make some noise!
アイアイアイヘッチュー　なななななんですの
I-I-I hate you! W-W-W-What is this?
キミがいなけりゃ　アタシはナイナイ
Without you, I'm nothing at all.
アイアイソーデスネ　その通りです
Yes, yes, that's right! Exactly as you say!
喉を過ぎれば　それは真実
Once it passes down my throat, it becomes the truth.
ああるべき場所へ　アタシ導く
To where it ought to be, it guides me.
奈落の底で　アイアイアイヘッチューなんですの
At the bottom of the abyss, I-I-I hate you! What is this?
キミにアイアイアイヘッチュー　なななななんですの
I-I-I hate you! W-W-W-What is this?
やはり軽薄　顔の大きなアタシ
As expected, shallow—me with my grand posture,
渇いたソコヘ引きずのる
dragging it into that dry place.
キミがいまかいまかと高嶺のソープ SECRET
You waiting impatiently for that high-altitude soap... secret!
愛に滲んだ衝動が　喉をヤケドさせる GREAT SECRET
An impulse soaked in love burns my throat. Great secret!
マニアウ？
Will I make it in time?
出てこないで！
Don't come out!
アイアイアイヘッチュー　なななななんですの
I-I-I hate you! W-W-W-What is this?
キミがいるからアタシはタイタイ
Because you're here, I am equal.
アイアイソーデスネ　その通りです
Yes, yes, that's right! Exactly as you say!
欲望のまま保持したくの
I want to hold onto it just as my desires dictate.
どうにもならない　アイアイアイヘッチュー
Nothing can be done about it! I-I-I hate you!
なななななんですの
W-W-W-What is this?
キミがいなけりゃ　アタシはナイナイ
Without you, I'm nothing at all.
アイアイソーデスネ　その通りです
Yes, yes, that's right! Exactly as you say!
喉を過ぎれば　それは真実
Once it passes down my throat, it becomes the truth.
ああるべき場所へ　アタシ導く
To where it ought to be, it guides me.
奈落の底で
At the bottom of the abyss...
Oh, such a misguided fool.
Your reckless ways have brought black doom upon yourself and those most beloved around you.
Blaming your misery on others when your demise was, in fact, forged by your own hands.
While you have earned your death in full,
it is with pity, not anger, that this blade falls upon you.
炉心融解
[Meltdown]
街明かり華やか エーテルの麻酔の冷たさ
The bustling city and its neon lights, a touch of ether that's cold as ice
眠れない午前二時 全てが急速に変わる
It's 2 AM and I can hardly sleep 'cause everything keeps changing rapidly
オイル切れのライター
I'm like a lighter that's all out of gas
焼けつくような胃の中
My insides are on fire
全てがそう嘘なら
If only everything was a lie
本当によかったのにね
Things would be so much better
君の首を絞める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck
光の溢れる昼下がり
On a bright, sunny afternoon
君の細い喉が跳ねるのを
I watched your slender throat twitch
泣き出しそうな眼で見ていた
As my eyes welled up with tears
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor
真っ青な光包まれて綺麗
And its pale blue light would envelop me so beautifully
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
そしたらすべてが許されるような気がして
Then everything might be okay, I might be forgiven
ベランダの向こう側 階段を昇っていく音
On the other side of the veranda, I hear footsteps ascending the stairs
陰り出した空が 窓ガラスに部屋に落ちる
As the clouds creep over the sunlight, it drips through my window and into my room
拡散する夕暮れ 泣き腫らしたような陽の赤
Twilight scatters across the horizon, red like eyes swollen by tears
溶けるように少しずつ
Slowly but surely, it's melting away
少しずつ死んでゆく世界
Slowly but steadily, the world is dying
君の首を絞める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck
春風に揺れるカーテン
My curtains were swaying gently in the spring breeze
乾いて切れた唇から
Your dry, parched lips mustered up
こぼれる言葉は泡のよう
Words that would vanish like foam on the waves
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor
真っ白に記憶融かされて消える
Into the shining, white light my memories will fade and disappear
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
また昔みたいに眠れるような そんな気がして
I might be able to sleep like I used to and everything might be okay
時計の秒針や テレビの司会者や
The second hand on the clock, and the host on the television
そこにいるけど
There's someone there
見えない誰かの
But I just can't see them
笑い声 飽和して反響する
Their laughter swells and grows into an endless echo
アレグロ・アジテート
Allegro agitate
耳鳴りが消えない 止まらない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
Allegro agitato
耳鳴りが消えない 止まない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
街の灯が消えてく夢を見た
I had a dream where the whole entire world disappeared
真夜中の部屋の広さと
Tonight, I'm swallowed by the vastness of my dark room
静寂が胸につっかえて
Yet, silence closes in and suffocates me
上手く息ができなくなる
My lungs can't find the air I need to breathe
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
そしたらきっと眠るように消えていけるんだ
Then I could finally fade away, as easily as closing my eyes to sleep
僕のいない朝は 今よりずっと素晴らしくて
A new dawn without me would surely be a dazzling new day
全ての歯車が噛み合い
All of the gears would be turning together in harmony
きっとそんな世界だ
Surely, that's how the world would be
Hi, darlings! And welcome to my 3D concert,
my first technically solo one.
As you can see up here,
is the hashtag for today,
which is #RequiemforLove3D!
I'm watching the chat. Did you guys enjoy it?
Did you like it? Did you have fun?
I sure hope so!
Well, obviously a lot just happened,
but I must let you all know this was all a musical.
So none of it was real.
No one is hurt.
There were no hololive girls hurt in the making of this musical,
so please don't worry!
This stage is awesome,
so I want to give it up to the team over at hololive production
who put this all together.
Can we just take a look,
take a moment to admire this beautiful stage before us?
Some of the more lesser-shown details
I kind of wanted to highlight a little bit.
So, let's go ahead and take a look at
perhaps the moon, maybe?
Look at that big thing in the background.
It was also dark red at one point,
but currently it is, as it probably should be,
normal, beautiful, because I was killed, so...
We also have the giant castle in the background,
which is, oh my gosh, I was so excited for this.
I was like, "Oh, I want something that's really kind of
cathedral-esque and dark and gothic,"
and they fully delivered.
I'm so, so pleased with how it ended up looking in the final,
so happy.
We also have the beautiful stained glass.
If you take a look,
it's back there.
These ones were actually screens,
but we also have the ones on the side
that were a little bit broken, but could also change as well.
Very, very fun.
It was kind of something that I was like, "Oh, I wonder how it's gonna go,"
but I think it ended up looking really cool, right?
Lastly, we have all of these lovely flowers
out in front.
I just thought they came out so pretty,
and I like how they kind of change throughout.
So it just kind of looked like nothingness,
like a little void of like dead plants,
but then at the end, they all bloomed and it was so beautiful!
Oh my gosh, I was so nervous!
And you might have noticed something's a little different about me today.
Do you see anything different?
My wings are out!
I decided, since we've known each other for kind of a long time now,
that maybe it was finally time to...
stop pretending they're a coat
and actually show you what they were.
But I did decide to take off my arm warmers a little bit,
just 'cause, you know, I was feeling a little warm after all of that movement.
So I'd love to show you the wings.
So I'm going to open them up for you and try flying for a little bit, so...
Yeah, there we go!
What do you think? I am capable...
of flight.
Obviously, it's a little...
It's a little slow,
but I'm working on it. I'm- I'm working on my muscles.
So, we'll- I'll figure it out eventually. It's been a while.
I was locked up for like 9,000 years. Cut me some slack.
Well, this is all very exciting.
So again, I'm so happy to have you here.
I wanted to talk a little bit about... I have an announcement after this, but before that,
I wanted to talk a little bit about uh just the making of this. Whoa.
We had so many lovely guests, first and foremost.
Uh first, we started off with Shiori Novella, who was our beautiful, cute witch who came here maybe not knowing what she was getting into.
Then, we had uh Takanashi Kiara, the brave, amazing phoenix,
came in trying to avenge her friend, but ended up getting bested by the best.
Then, we had IRyS, my Nephilim friend, friends as we're both demons, kind of.
And then, last but not least, of course, we had the Calliope Mori come in and uh take my life, as she should have, because wow.
I was kind of- I was kind of mean in that musical, don't you think?
Not- not exactly the way that I usually am so kind, but...
But regardless, it was really fun.
Uh I came up with the idea for the story, and I wanted something that was like a little more exciting, a little more chuunibyou.
'Cause deep down, I am cringe,
but I am free, so...
I hope you enjoyed the concept. We had amazing scriptwriters,
and just the whole team working on all of this was so amazing. So thank you for everyone who put in their efforts into this.
Seriously means so much to me, and uh audience, Jailbirds,
thank you so much for watching. I hope you had a wonderful time.
And now, it is time for an important announcement!
This is my celebration merch! Nerissa Ravencroft 850,000 Subscribers Celebration!
So uh let's go ahead and take a look at the details.
Next up, or first up, I suppose,
"Your assignment has arrived."
This is a plush blanket featuring an illustration by
basically my second mama, Yomosaka at this point, who also did the promotional art,
or the- the like main cover art for this musical today.
Um so it's very lovely. All of the uh merch today is going to be themed
off of the DEO outfit.
Again, so beautiful,
so gorgeous. You can cuddle up with it at night if you're feeling lonesome.
So highly recommend grabbing it.
Next up,
we have the uh DEO Nerissa Voice Keychain.
This illustration is by noka.
This is a cute keychain, of course. You can carry it around with you everywhere, and
in case you miss the sound of my voice,
it has my voice in it! About six different voice samples,
so you can click, click, click, click, click and hear me say different varying, funny little things.
So do consider it.
Next up is the Nerissa Ravencroft Hand Puppet.
Um I really wanted one, and I thought you guys would too,
and especially with the sexy DEO outfit, I just thought it made sense.
So do think about the puppet shows that you could put on with me
as your starring puppet.
Think about it. Consider the possibilities.
So that is the first one... or first one, that is one of the last ones. But next up
is the last item, which is the "Match with Me!" Necklace.
This features the necklace from my DEO outfit.
It is silver, and it has a uh tiny amethyst-colored gem,
because it's kind of hard to tell, but the gem on my actual necklace is not red. It is actually kind of purplish.
So please look forward to it.
Next up is the Complete Set Purchase Bonus,
limited edition version.
Uh it's going to come with a postcard with a handwritten autograph by yours truly,
and of course, the art is going to be the same one that's featured in the plush blanket, the art by Yomosaka-san.
So please do consider getting it uh if you want the whole set, if you want the limited set.
Um next up is the regular complete set.
This is going to come with a postcard with a duplicated foil-stamped autograph by me,
in the case that you miss out on the limited, but you'll still get my signature either way, so don't worry too much.
And uh both the limited and complete set are going to be coming with
a bonus voice pack called "A Late Night at the Office,"
featuring me, of course, and you, who works in my office, Jailbird.
So that is all of my merchandise.
Please, please buy it. I hope you like it. Again, this is a celebration for 850,000K,
and I would be remiss to not say that this is all thanks to you guys and your support. So thank you so so much for supporting me, for...
following me, for...
watching my covers, for watching this today,
watching my streams, commenting,
everything you guys do, I am so grateful.
So, thank you so much! So,
that's the... the final full set.
And... and yeah! It's... it's all good. So, please buy it!
I hope you guys like it. I hope you're looking forward
to receiving the items if you're buying it.
They will go live right after this, I believe.
So, go ahead and check the description. It should have all the information right below.
So, thank you all so much!
And that's that. So,
I guess I should say goodbye.
So... I don't want to, though.
I'm having so much fun today dancing with everyone and singing for you guys, and...
But I'm so grateful I could spend time with you and share this special moment with you.
I hope you guys all had a lot of fun,
and I look forward to seeing you all in my next stream.
So, for now, bye-bye, darlings!
REQUIEM for LOVE
[Title: REQUIEM for LOVE]